SRIRAM PK

Product Designer www.srirampk.com

ABOUT ME

I'm a UI/UX/IX Designer and Prototyper. I'm passionate about User centered design and love crafting products that solve real problems.

I research, communicate, prototype, design, test, document and deliver.

I have 3 and half years of enterprise experience that includes an internship at a design agency(Monigle).

PORTFOLIO

www.srirampk.com

EMAIL uxsriram@gmail.com

SKILLS

DESIGN

Storyboarding, Journey mapping, User personas, Wireframing, Interactive prototypes, Mockups, Information Architecture, Visual design

RESEARCH

A/B testing, Contextual inquiry, Wizard of Oz, Affinity diagrams, Flow and sequence models, Think alouds, Heuristic evaluation, Web analytics, Surveys and Usability an<u>alysis</u>.

TOOLS

DESIGN PROTOTYPING

Sketch Invision
Photoshop Framer JS
Illustrator Principle
Balsamiq Marvel
Justinmind Axure
Zeplin

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer, Apple, Inc., CA

September 2018 - Present

- Contributing to the UX & UI of apple's internal product development teams.
- Responsible for stakeholder interviews, client presentations, mockups, design deliverables.

UI/UX Design Intern, Monigle, Denver, CO

May 2018 - August 2018

- Contributed to the UX & UI of new BEAM product features
- Guided the management, layout and loading of content to client brand management systems
- Worked closely in support of internal development, product and client experience teams

Product Designer, Pobyt

June 2017 - May 2018

- Solely responsible for product strategy product design and user experience of Pobyt, a hotel reservation app for short stays.
- Followed agile approach: user interviews, design, feedback and rapid iterations
- Managed a team of 8 (designers and developers)

Business Analyst, S&P Global Market Intelligence

Jun 2015 - Dec 2016

- Worked on designing user interfaces for their data collection web applications.
- Notable projects include Celsus, GICS and Hub.
- Worked closely with the QA team to evaluate the usability of the product.

Design Intern, Etyacol Technologies

Jan 2015 - June 2015

Responsible for User Interface Design of Cashkumar web application and dashboard. Created several graphic design posters for social media engagement.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina, Charlotte, USA M.S., Human Computer Interaction

Jan 2017 - June 2018

Vellore Institute of Technology, India M.S.,Software Engineering

June 2010 - May 2015